
// Videogames quiz questions
const questionsVideogames = [
    {
        question: 'What is the best selling video game?',
        answers:['Overwatch', 'Call of Duty', 'Minecraft', 'FIFA'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the best selling video game console to date?',
        answers:['PlayStation2', 'Nintendo Switch', 'Xbox 360', 'Sega Mega Drive'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: 'Which of the following is the most expensive made video game?',
        answers:['Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 2', 'Final Fantasy VII', 'Battlefield4', 'Grand Theft Auto V'],
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: 'In which month of 2020 was PS5 released?',
        answers:['January', 'June', 'September', 'November'],
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: 'Which one is the most famous mobile phone game of all times?',
        answers:['Tetris', 'Snake', 'Candy Crush', 'Angry Birds'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: 'When was Mario Bros released?',
        answers:['1996', '1985', '1983', '1988'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: ' Which fruit do you collect in Crash Bandicoot?',
        answers:['Apples', 'Mangos', 'Guavas', 'Wumpa Fruits'],
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: ' What is the name of the main charachter in Horizon Zero Dawn?',
        answers:['Aloy', 'Rost', 'Avad', 'Lea'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: ' Which company is the developer and publisher of Legend of Zelda?',
        answers:['Konami', 'Nintendo', 'Sony', 'Activision'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: ' Which Overwatch hero says "One shot, One kill."?',
        answers:['Mei', 'Winston', 'Widowmaker', 'Zarya'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: ' Who is the most famous video game charachter of all times?',
        answers:['Link', 'Tracer', 'Sonic', 'Mario'],
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: ' Kratos is the main charachter of which video game?',
        answers:['God of War', 'Call of Duty', 'God Hand', 'Red Dead Redemption'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: ' In which console was the first Final Fantasy released?',
        answers:['PlayStation', 'Xbox', 'Nintendo', 'Odyssey'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: 'Which arcade video game is the highest grossing?',
        answers:['Donkey Kong', 'Pac-Man', 'Asteroids', 'Battlezone'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: 'Which video game is considered the worst video game created?',
        answers:['None', 'Finaly Fantasy XIV', 'Atari E.T.', 'SimCity'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    }
];

// Movies quiz questions
const questionsMovies = [
    {
        question: 'What is the most expensive movie ever made?',
        answers:['Avengers: Age of Ultrons', 'Justice League', 'Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides', 'SpiderMan 3'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: 'How many golden tickets were hidden inside Wonka bars in Willy Wonka & The Chocolate Factory?',
        answers:['3', '5', '8', '11'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: "In the Avengers movies, what is the name of Thor's hammer?",
        answers:['Milfred', 'Magni','Mjölnir' ,'Lokasenna'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial:  What's the name of E.T. terrestrial friend?",
        answers:['Elliot', 'Elia', 'Ethan', 'Ernest'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: 'Back to the Future: To which year does Marty McFly travel back in time?',
        answers:['1985', '1955', '1920', '2015'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: 'What is Indiana Jones everyday job?',
        answers:['Unmployed', 'Liontamer', 'Professor of Archeologist', 'Cowboy'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: ' Which character says "I am your father?"',
        answers:['Father Ted', 'Luke Skywalker', 'My Dad?', 'Darth Vader'],
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: ' In Avengers the End Game: Who sacrifices themselves for the Soul Stone?',
        answers:['Natacha Romanoff', 'Clint Barton', 'Nebula', 'Tony Stark'],
        correctAnswer: 1,
    },

    {
        question: "What is the name of the little girl who steals Wrecked Ralph's Medal?",
        answers:['Penelope Cruz', 'Vanellope von Schweetz', 'Princess Pach', 'Ms Pac-Man'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: ' Which Disney princess dresses as a man to save her father?',
        answers:['Jasmine', 'Belle', 'Mulan', 'Merida'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: ' What is the name of the fictional island Jurassic Park is situated on?',
        answers:['Isla Bonita', 'Isla Nera', 'Coney Island', 'Isla Nublar'],
        correctAnswer: 4,
    },

    {
        question: ' What happens to Mogwai ("The Gremilins") when they get wet? ',
        answers:['Become evil', 'Multiply', 'Cath a cold', 'Get hungry'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: ' Which movie contains the famous quote "Redrum. Redrum. REDRUM!"',
        answers:['The Blair Witch Project', 'Scream', 'Shining ', 'Suspiria'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    },

    {
        question: '"My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die.” Who killed Inigo’s father?',
        answers:['Vizzini', 'Count Rugen', 'Dread Pirate Roberts', 'Buttercup'],
        correctAnswer: 2,
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the highest-grossing movie of all times?',
        answers:['Titanic', 'Avengers: Endgame', 'Avatar', 'Star Wars: The Force Awakens'],
        correctAnswer: 3,
    }
];